[Music]
Hello friends, welcome to the market.
Friends, in this video we will
talk about the quarter four results of ICICI Lobart.
Subscribe to the channel to
see the results first.   Be it the
results of Quarter Four or any other news,
you will get to see it first on our channel.
So, let's see
what updates there are from the company.  So, finally here the company has
also announced the final dividend
for you.  If you have this stock,
please let us know by writing in the comments.  So here is
how much dividend the
company has finally given.  So here you can see that the
company has given you a dividend of ₹7 per share
as per the face value of ₹10.
So the company is giving a very good dividend here.
So here we go over the company's
results.  How have the company's
results come this time?  So if
you look here, the company's results are being
shown to us here.  Company details are
given here.  How much profit has the company made here
in the last year?  So
friends, let us now talk
about the chart pattern of the results of Quarter Four,
sorry, let us understand according to the financial balance sheet,
what kind of
results are seen coming here.  So if we
look at it in comparison to last year, then here
in March 24, as per last year, from March 25,
you can see that the
company had generated revenue of around Rs 516000.   The
total income last year was Rs 585000, which has increased this year to Rs
585000. If
seen in this way, the profit and income of the company has been
seen increasing.  If we
talk about the profit of the company on quarter-on-quarter basis,
it has been
seen to be slightly normal.
After this, if we talk about
how much the total expenditure of the company has been on this, then
look at this, last year the company's expenditure was
around Rs 480000.  Accordingly, if we look at the company this time, the
company's
expenses have been seen here at Rs 543000.  If seen in this way, then
normally the company's
profit will also be made here.  If
we talk about the profit of the company,
here we will subtract the expenses from the total income
plus the tax, then
we will get the profit of the company here.
So if you look here,
all the knowledge about the company is given, which includes the
expenses of other assets of the company
etc.  That too has been minused.
Now let us discuss how much profit the company has made.
So
lastly, let us discuss here the total profit that the company is getting.
So friends, the total profit of the company here,
last year the
profit that the company was making here was
seen to be around Rs 56000.  This
time the company is
seeing a profit of Rs 41,592.   If
seen from this perspective, the profit of the company is
seen falling since last year
and is also seen falling since the last quarter.
So normally the company has
not got very good results here.  But it will be
said that here the company has given a very good
dividend and if
seen from our perspective as per last year, the assets of the company have
increased.  According to that, the company is
seen making a good profit.
Thank you.